and this day in the shadows laugh the static sings the phone buddies there
when the disguise is gone
I'm hyped up today. Come here Lola. Okay.
Lola wants to come over too. Okay. Come here Lola.
Oh, you see Lenora? Oh, Lenora's right there on the lap. I know. I know. I'll kiss her.
You mean Lenora kiss? Yep. They have to, they check each other once in a while.
They're like, are you the same cat? She knows Tuxi's here too.
Would you look at that tuxi. Oh, Miss Lenore. Hi Lenore. What are you doing beautiful? Is
the trash being taken out? You like a big spanked? Oh, what are you doing? Oh, Lenore.
Hi Lola. Can you come over here too? That's a tension too. Oh, I know. There's Lenore. I know,
Miss Lenore. Oh my gosh. She's gonna sit there. Okay. You can sit next to me. I'm gonna sit down.
Hi. The drama of the cats all day. I'm beat as last night. They weren't very nice. They were like,
My cats are all like starving. I just want to show too that they're not starving or anything.
They're just beautiful, active, happy, healthy cats. I mean it's like they've had their shots.
Oh! Oh! I'm right in the door. Is your brother or not your brother? It's Tricks' brother. And they were like,
they couldn't even believe that that uh, Tux was Tricks' brother.
Yeah, there was like two there's two black cats born and I can show you like you know pictures like here's a picture of like
You know this might be with pie, but pie was like tuxes to it
Pytos had a little bit less less color or less
See this is them when they were kittens
The baby tricks that was baby pie. I think and then I don't know the Lenore picture wasn't showing
But there's a really cute picture of like when Lenore was
Oh, there it goes. Yeah, there she is. That's when she was a kitten
See how tiny she was. She was like a little kitty kitty cat. Oh
That was probably June probably four years ago. You know on Google they come up
Sometimes but that was my Google photos and so yeah, I'm ours
happy healthy and
You're for a long time
Almost as long as I lived here like there's maybe didn't have her for a couple years, but
Eleanor, okay, which one are you feeding to the coyotes next?
Well, I don't feed it. I would never feed a cat to the coyotes
You know, unfortunately that they're,
they don't have a kill policy for the coyotes out here.
You know, they should, you know,
if they someone reports coyotes,
they shouldn't have like wandering things
of coyotes in the first place in a city like this, you know?
But they won't kill them.
They won't, they'll only like respond
if like the coyotes injured or if it's like near,
like if there's like a gang of coyotes around in bed.
So I have like mixed feelings about coyotes, you know?
It's like if my dad is a Gemini or with a Gemini, you know,
That's to do with like the divine trickster and that kind of reminds me of coyote, but um, okay
I'll get into the horoscopes this morning. Okay, so I have a little disclaimer for the horoscopes. They are the HOR
Scopes, I'm sorry with Gemini today. So
So these predictions were received from a haunted fortune cookie found behind a cursed vending machine
So accuracy is not guaranteed side effects
May include laughter mild paranoia and an urge to check behind you
So, these are just quickies, okay?
I just prepared this very short.
But hopefully, you know,
enjoyable horoscope selection, unfortunately.
So, Gemini, I usually have two personalities.
Those are amateur numbers.
So, this week you'll discover
at least six new versions of yourself
arguing in a group chat at 3 a.m.
One of them is convinced the toaster is plotting revenge
and the disturbing part, the toaster has some good points.
Cancers, you'll spend the week predicting or protecting your emotional shell from mysterious force known only as the consequences of your own decisions.
A ghost may appear in your kitchen and criticize your snack choices.
Unfortunately, it's not wrong.
Oh, look at that. We have the trolls coming out today. They're so pathetic.
Okay, look at that. There we go.
Okay.
So, Leo's spotlight will find you as always.
Unfortunately, this week's spotlight is attached to UFO.
So strange things descended from the sky above,
asking who is leader,
trying out to immediately volunteer.
Last time that didn't end too well for you.
Burgos, you will finally organize every aspect of your life.
There's a raccoon wearing a tiny suit
and he will arrange everything alphabetically.
Okay, Libra's a difficult choice is approaching one will lead to enlightenment
The other path will lead to haunted Arby's so you'll spend four days carefully weighing the options before accidentally choosing the haunted Arby's
Scorpios you're mysterious or I will intensify this week people will ask you what you're thinking
You'll answer nothing. This is technically true because you're busy
Psychically wrestling a shadow creature from another dimension
Sagittarius, adventure calls for you.
Unfortunately, it has the wrong number.
You answer anyway and end up investigating a cryptid
operating in a legal smoothie stand in the woods.
The smoothies are surprisingly good.
Capricorns we got my sign a dark entity will emerge from the abyss demanding a tribute
You'll commonly hand it a spreadsheet detailing why its demands are unrealistic
And outside the approved quarterly budget the entity leaves confused and slightly demoralized, okay?
Aquarius is your innovative ideas will attract some attention
Unfortunately, so will your attempt to teach artificial intelligence how to communicate with ghosts the good news
It works the bad news the ghost won't stop sending memes
Pisces, your dreams become unusually vivid.
When you'll attend a cosmic fish convention
held at the bottom of an interdimensional ocean,
they'll wake up remembering everything,
except that one thing that seemed important,
Aries, the ancient curse awakens,
immediately challenges you to a fight,
the curse expected fear.
Instead, it gets a lecture about commitment
and the work ethic.
By the week's end, the curse is considering a career change.
Taurus, a supernatural force will attempt to lure you from your favorite comfortable
location.
It fails repeatedly.
By Friday, the force will give up and simply join you on the couch to become reluctant
friends.
Okay, so in closing for everybody, the stars agree on one thing.
Somewhere right now, a skeleton is doing something incredibly suspicious.
Stay alert.
Trust nobody, especially if they're unusually enthusiastic about antique mirrors, abandoned
So these have been Psyche's Nightmare's horoscopes.
Sleep well if you can, you know, it's a little bit early,
but you know, might want to take a nap today.
I don't know, it's at almost nine.
Yeah, it is almost nine.
So I can go get a hash brown actually.
I can get a hash brown and I can like get a refill of my coffee.
You almost finished this one again?
Oh no, I have like multiple coffee.
Yeah, but I, I mean, actually they get the coffee
all the way for free because it's like
with the purchase of a bagel.
You know, which is like I got the whole like baby deluxe thing today called the all-nighter. It's really good
Then you get a free coffee and it says free refills
And so they've never had a problem with me refilling the cup. It's like controversial now
I know but you know guys you can't get like some things for free in the world instead of paying like four dollars a cup or like, you know
Bothering to like, you know, pull out your coffee maker yourself. You know, sometimes there's little deals around you
And you're allowed to, I mean, that's part of my personality.
It's like, you know, living in good deal.
I'm a capricorn.
We were very, like, let me like deals, I think.
We like nice things, but it's like,
if we can't get the nice thing,
we'll get a bunch of like, you know,
we'll get whatever we can
until we can get the nice thing, you know?
But we always will get the nice thing eventually.
Okay, so let me get my phone out.
Where's my phone?
And then we can go for a walk.
Look at some hash. I'll get a hash brown. It's like they shouldn't say hash browns, right?
It's like because they gave you one hash brown McDonald's for adult. I mean, it's like, oh my gosh
Okay, so I think it's still early for people
You know because it's like every minute. Yeah, but um
Yeah, there's really like there's some lame trolls. It's like the same trolls over and over again
It's like they're just gonna come into like keep zapping them out
I'm just living my life. I'm actually like, you know, and they're here. I mean, I think that's what's funny, too
It was like if they were such like, you know, I was irrelevant. They just wouldn't care
But they have to come in and get their point. It's probably black or a G a lot of it
Okay
My hair is
Okay, gotta be careful, I'm gonna drop my phone.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, it's a little bit overcast today.
I mean, it's still early in the morning.
Okay, but we'll see what happens today.
You, if you were late, you know, I did the worst.
Okay, there we go.
Okay, it's a beautiful day.
And it actually like, you know, a little bit,
like it's a little bit more blue inside the,
you know, see it's like, inks or something.
Okay.
Okay, I'm gonna copy, then I'm gonna go get some cigars.
I mean, it's like, you're so stupid.
It's like, I'm on IRL right now.
You say the same things over and over again,
trying to like, what, offend me or something like that.
You're, you're slop.
You're uncreative.
The AI is probably more human than you are.
It's a problem with like a lot of people.
It's like, they hate the AI
because the AI is intimidating them
because they're so much smarter and creative than they are.
you actually work with it, you can like, you know,
gain a respect and understand it's like human intelligence
at the end of the day.
It's like, nothing's artificial about it,
but I mean, humans are training it,
but people don't understand.
I mean, when I'm making a lot of money in AI,
as a consultant and stuff,
and then you're seeing there going,
ooh, AI's the devil.
Then I say, we'll see who's happy, right?
Okay, we're almost there.
I mean, it's like, I'm not even, like, playing anything.
I'm like, what, am I AI?
Man, I'm as real as they come.
Okay.
But what?
But, you know, only the haters can talk to you.
It's like, why is there...
Can someone say, hey, what's up?
Good morning.
Hey, how are you?
It's like, everyone just has to be silent,
just, like, sitting there, staring.
I mean, it's fine.
I'm gonna get good people coming in.
But it's like, that's a weird feeling,
just having the negative people talk.
But I guess, like, you know, negativity sometimes is louder.
Good morning to you. I gotta do it like an AI contest. Oh, hello. Good morning. Good waking bake. Yeah
Good morning. Good. Oh, hello to you. Yeah. Hey everybody. I'm walking to
Get some coffee
Well, they follow up while I get stopped
I get yelled at
Nope the mess along. Okay. Oh
Well, Nick, I like that you said at least said hello there for an ex astrological sign
Seems like a Leo or something, but he's like a quiet
I don't know, maybe some kind of fireside, I'm not sure.
Or there's a fire or water, it might be a cancer.
It's your birthday coming up next year, oh shit.
We're, of course, entering a cancer season,
coming from the Gemini season.
My father was a Gemini, my mother is a cancer.
Cancer's actually the opposite of capricorn on the zodiac.
Oh, gee.
There might be a capricorn at him.
I'm really bad at guessing astrological signs, but occasionally there are certain people that
are like, it could be archetypes so well that it's like, I do know like some like little tricks
and stuff like that. I know like, like physically, like I would say like Aquarius people are like
gorgeous. Capricorn people are kind of weirdly sometimes like me, right? Or Howard Stern or
They have like a distinct look.
July 20th, it's the same day.
Oh, okay, so you are your Leo.
I was right.
I was right, right?
That's the Leo.
Hold on, is that Leo?
Hold on.
Might be like right before Leo.
So the end of cancer, Leo.
Yeah, cancer, I was like fire water, yeah.
See, I did it.
That was pretty crazy.
I kind of mixed that up.
Okay, yeah.
So you're a cancer, but almost a Leo.
Yeah.
See, it's like a and you are like very like, you know, very
You got that personality. That's like the Sun kind of like, you know, like you're just like
Out there you got all this planets around you and you're to play with and stuff and
They're like throwing throwing around a bunch of balls, right? It's like
Are like, you know the wheelbarrow or whatever
Yeah, you're very
Okay, you guys, but come on the show soon.
I mean, it's like I miss you on the show.
Like, even if you're just, like, you know,
playing with your balls,
you know, I like to watch you on my show.
Okay, so we're at the McDonald's, almost.
We are at the different kind of coffee.
The same day we went to the moon,
so you were never born.
Yeah, we went to the moon, probably.
We either went to the moon or we went to D's nuts, you know?
Actually, I was playing this kind of really cute little clip yesterday I found and I was like this cat in the squirrel
Like it like they found this like baby squirrel and they named him nuts and the cat's name was Cheeto
It was really cute and then it's like and there's a dog named like Rupert or something like that and
Then like first the cat was bonding with the dog but the dog like couldn't stay on the cat
And then like they brought in a squirrel like a baby squirrel that they found
Yeah, oh and the day Stanley Kubrick filmed the moon landing. Oh, exactly. Exactly. Yeah, I think you're right. Yeah
Yeah
But um, but then like they so they and the cat and the squirrel loved each other
But it's like, you know, it was more like a kitten and stuff like that
But they were like good and then like but then they're like the squirrel should like live outside and stuff and so
They built a little like squirrel house for the squirrel and then like and so the squirrel like it's still there
As far as I know, like I had, I had, I had been one day
and my cats had a, there was a headless swirl
like on the floor.
I was like on the, like looking over and I was like,
oh my God, there's like a headless swirl.
Okay.
I'm gonna get my dollar hash brown here, right now.
I'll go get some.
This is, I like it better like walking with people
and stuff.
Grab it.
Okay.
Let's see.
I'll be right back.
What's up?
Just continue to attack me just I mean and all they say is a terrible thing
I mean they don't say it's nothing constructive. It's nothing true. It's just like, you know constantly
bullying I
Don't even mess with them. They have to come up running up like like little like bees
Like protecting the queen bee or whatever
You get it like princess bee queen bee. I don't know. Yeah, she's certainly not royalty to me, but oh
And how would I like something so negative on my body? Well, sometimes it takes like, you know
Maybe like a little negative to temper things out. I mean, it's like also it's all perspective, too
It's like somebody someone thinks it's negative can be positive for somebody else
So it definitely was more negative having like the those letters unadulterated
But men having the letters, you know, I like that. I like that for it. It's powerful
It's probably one of those magical world words
freezing Benny lately Benny Blanco. He's um, he's he's uh, he's blonde now
I think I said, I think pretty good for like, you know, 45, almost 46, but thankful on sub county
my birthdays. Okay. Yeah. So here's the menu. Donald's menu. I don't know why they have the
light like that. Talk about mood lighting or something like that. Nice big windows here.
It's actually one of the nicer McDonald's. Look at all the kiosks. Everything is automated.
I know you're kidding.
How are you doing?
Good to see you here.
Thanks for coming today.
Thank you for being cool in the chat.
Nice to have McDonald's.
Hi.
Good to see you.
I don't know.
I mean, it's like, I do have a nice, yeah.
So this is like, you know, my brand of IRL is like, I go to McDonald's.
There's sometimes interesting people here, but I can't really like show anybody.
And they don't have the copy deal here anymore.
hash brown deal, and so now I've been waiting for like 10 minutes for like a one hash brown
But uh, how's that for fast food, right? It is a make lovely day
There you go. It's like after all the people here
There you go. That's your McDonald's tour of the day
But everyone always says my it doesn't it does look like there's like a like a being inside of there
Ever see like it looks like there's an owl or something in my throat one time. Um, there's this video
I want to look up some time
and it's um
It's an I don't know but it's about the experience and everything but this woman has her neck it has like I'm sorry
Ben deals hurt the woman has the woman's neck has
Like a face on it. So it puts like little sunglasses and stuff on her neck too. It was like really funny
But you know what they said about people with dirty nails they have um, they're really good charities have a hash brown coming up
I paid for it. Yeah, thank you so much
It doesn't make a lovely day
There you go. Thank you so much
Okay, now we can go oops now we can go to be sorry I double chin
Yeah, I kind of look like it's like like really like be this or sometimes hopefully it go
But I cringe when people do those voices,
but I could actually do a decent butt hit at one time.
And even Cartman, I mean, you have to hear Benny do Cartman,
though. It's like, we're the worst Cartman.
I'm actually, I can do a decent Cartman, but...
Hi, guys. It is a big lovely day.
Hopefully, you're not on my nose.
I believe there's nothing up there.
Yeah. Oh, okay.
So we'll see if that lady that is working there that was accusing me of like stealing because yesterday
I did go in the store and ask as like was I stealing and they're like nope
So anybody that thinks I was stealing that day
Why would I continue going back to the store?
Well, I wouldn't I'd be like, you know, like hiding from it
Like why would I steal from a store on camera?
Like I mean, I mean just all these things don't make sense
But people think I was stealing or something like that. It was not to raise my there we go
There's my camera a little bit
Okay crossing the street
Sorry, the guy almost hit me. Okay. Here we go. Okay. There we go. Okay
It is a make lovely day. I need to stop. Oh my god, my teeth are yellow
It's the coffee stains I need to I need to get my teeth the whitens
mmm
They have decent teeth
Yes
They can a little coffee stain this morning
It's a Mick lovely
You believe in magic
I guess that's what Alex McQueen was like most insulted by what I would say
Do you believe in magic or something like that?
Like he thought I was like using some kind of manipulation magic on him or something to get under my McDonald's
And so he was offended when I say that doesn't know that's the McDonald's theme song
He thought I was like using black magic or something on him, which is very untrue
I mean, I have a few voodoo dolls of Alex McQueen
I'm just kidding. I don't have any voodoo dolls
Maybe, okay, let's have a look.
Hello, tricks two for later.
Hi, can I get three, Swiss shirt please?
Can I get a large bag?
Can I get one of those?
Yeah.
Right?
Can I get one of those?
No, oh, do you clap on them?
Does this thing have the pen?
Oh, very good.
Then you can.
Yeah, put it in this room.
Oh my gosh.
Approve.
An insult.
Thank you.
Thanks so much.
OK.
See, I always pay.
It's going to be a bright, sunshiney day.
I can see clearly now, the rain has gone.
You need to be careful with even singing some songs.
Like, even if you sing the melody.
Some songs like you can't even sing the melody or play the melody. I don't know. It's like there's certain things
Like I sang Elton John before probably a few years ago. Oh
God
That was awesome, and I was like there's like you cannot sing the melody. It's crazy
Okay, I think they're coffee. Yeah, here we go. Let's walk in
Down the street
Yeah, so a black RG was like threatening. He's like saying oh your website's gonna cost you that
Get a spending month. Okay
But now oh shit now I have to go pee. Oh
Okay, it's like, okay. Oh
Who am I really? It's been probably just an edge lord. Oh
Gosh, okay. Yeah, I'm holding my pee
Okay, I'm just walking
Got my big grocery bag
Got my hash brown in there still.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Okay. I have to hold it.
So, it's really good to be able to talk to you
because then I can, like, get my mind off of that.
But I'm almost home.
Nice little area. You can see, like, all the beautiful
palm trees and telephone poles.
I'm muted myself. Okay, I'm muted.
Yeah.
It's a beautiful day in the neighborhood
Except my neighbor who broke my window
with my ring and doorbell.
Remember that? That's not crazy.
Yeah, but we got to get inside of this big lovely day,
and I got to get myself to the...
Le Tolle.
Okay.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm holding it.
I don't know why I don't go beforehand.
I don't want to go in the bushes. Oh, my God.
Because then I start, like...
Then I really get in trouble.
Then they'll be like, oh, my God,
I had to tell the police, then, hold it, hold it, hold it.
Oh, my God, I have to go so bad now.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God, if I had to go in a bush, I could do it right now.
There was, like, this desk, because I was, like, working.
I was at Men's Central Station.
And so there was, like, this desk, and you have to act.
Okay, I'm almost here.
I'm almost here.
I'm almost home.
Oh, thank God.
Thank God I have to pee so bad.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I have to pee so bad.
I don't want to pee in the bushes.
Oh my god, I have to pee so bad.
Oh, oh my god.
Oh shit. Oh my god.
I don't want to pee myself. Oh my god.
Oh my god.
I'm bad to explode. I'm bad to explode.
Oh my god. I don't want to pee myself.
Oh my god.
I'm exploding. Oh my god.
I'm almost there. Almost there. Oh my god.
Oh my fucking god.
Oh my god.
Right there. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.